What is it? It's dark.
Light was born within
The light is the sky and the sea
land and plants
Making animals and the moon and stars
We filled in the wasteland’s sluggish space.
Finally, of light
The seed has the powers of twelve animals
sent twelve angels to earth
manage those angels
By choosing humans
It made the world beautiful
Humans use the created light
It was orange as a signal.
Transforming the world at a rapid pace
succeeded
However, as the area of light becomes wider,
The area of darkness has shrunk
In the end, the darkness
Create demons to decorate the world
went out
Share the absolute power of the God of Light
The twelve angels who have
To protect the world from evil spirits
the battle began
momentary sacrifice
After countless gruesome battles
warriors in the end
succeeded in defeating the demons
Both their absolute power and their evil intentions.
Sealed inside the gates of hell
in the form of humans
We started living together
kid who
Did you always come?
Don't you need to talk to me?
uh
Oh, who was it?
This is Angel Capital. Angel
Ah
Ah, that angel, you are the boss.
Oh, it's deep.
Uh haha
Ah, but
What brought you here?
no what
I still can't contact you
I did some research and found out that you are here.
So I came here
Ah, here
It feels good to be working
It sounds nice
He came all the way here to get money.
Hehe, this is ridiculous.
Don't just go
Are you an angel because the kids ordered it?
Get rid of something
It's two billion before the taste starts to swell.
Interest of principal billion billion
And after today, 2.2 billion
It'll be fine
Interest is billion
If you pass it today, it will be 200 million more.
The business you operate
If you dispose of your car
I think it will be handled roughly.
Just sign here
I'll organize everything.
Uh huh huh huh
Hey me
To live and live to get money
This kind of thing that comes all the way to Kampang
This is my first time using a creative corpse.
uh
Hey, put away that scary piece of paper.
I want it too
But I can't repay you
Okay, go out later.
I work hard at my part-time job and earn money.
I'll pay back everything so far
Youngsu Cho
I'll say it again, yeah
Our angel capital
Thugs like the boss
gangster
Only for criminals
I will lend you money
That's why
It's surprisingly easy to get money.
No setbacks
For your information, let me tell you something:
For the past hundred years I
This
I never got paid while working
never been
one hundred years
It's a fairy tale in a hundred years
What the fuck is he
Fighting Fighting
Joo Hyung-soo, please deposit money, sir.
As you said, bail.
I just deposited 200 million won
I love you
This is Angel Capital.
Oh, I'm sorry, but
Our angel capital
General loans are a bit difficult. Crime
Power is present or present
illegal
Something like trying to get things done
Unless you are a risk taker
Trading is difficult
Maybe
Are you affiliated with an organized crime group?
Do you have a criminal record?
Oh no, you're not there
Then I'm sorry
It seems difficult to get a loan
Yes, look elsewhere.
Ah
Ha, I was here.
Okay
let's see
Ah, it's been a while since I warmed up, guys.
Everyone checked the video
Oh wait a minute
These guys are the boss
When there is liquid cash
We have to attack the scene.
I want to leave early
Okay okay
Let's go, let's go, have a good day
Don said he came straight to the scene.
I have to go quickly okay
Yes, Taeseon, it’s me.
Baby, how are you doing?
Uh haha you know
Well, I'm thinking of you especially
I only care about you
It's a food condolence, kid.
You appeared in my dream last night
A big tiger appears
It was so nice to see you
It seems like you missed me a lot
Hahahaha
hello hello
I'm listening
Ahahahaha
What is he? How is your health?
Are you taking medication for depression again these days?
Oh, that's okay
Take care of your health uh
And if you need anything
Contact me right away
I need money again ah
yes I need it
I can't do it because I can't collect the money this month.
I'll give it to you next month
Because I'm busy right now
Yatae wait a minute wait a minute
Being human
There are times when you suddenly need money.
Live harder than your head
I have a lot of money and live a nice life
I'm not
No, what's cool about private tea?
Oh, and why does a detective need money?
Hey
Detective, man, he lives without spending money.
you
The detective is running around without money.
Ah, a thief and a psycho bastard and all.
Ignore the dog
Oh my
That's because I'm getting older and it's sad.
Oh you too
Hey, I'm 100 years older than you.
What are you doing when you don't go out?
When you're 100 years old, you'll be in the human world
We can't even meet each other, man
And I don't remember you there
To Byeongjaul
Give up on the barbarians
When I almost died because of it
how was it then
Don't you remember, I saved you
It was like that
I was so thankful back then
I'm still thankful for that
I will never forget such grace
That's the kind of person
That's the kind of relationship we have
Okay, just wait a moment.
Oh, I will definitely definitely go there. I trust you.
What is A?
Oh, I sent the money now.
I saved some money
Uh oh
ok thank you kid
What are you investigating?
That's because I need money
Well then I will never contact you again.
yes yes yes
Oh well then
There's a lot of stuff down there, okay.
I'm ready, let's go
After coming here
again
I was able to see a beautiful world
Due to degenerative changes in the membrane
I've been blind for the past three years
In eternity
There's no hope
I did it but really
Especially handsome and kind like an angel.
Nurse Department
After consulting
By all means
At Taishan Hanyeon
I want to get treatment
I gain confidence
Hello
Hey, you're not leaving
Because I'm away right now
Donnie's AI secretary takes over
I received it
Please tell me your business
I'll pass it on to you
Ah, teacher
Please help me, why are you doing this again?
Mr. Drop, Mr.
Ah
Oh, go get treatment.
Hey bell
I told you to do it gently
All the patients are running away.
You have a child
The person at the scene is okay.
Go now
Oh, it's okay, oh oh
Oh oh oh oh
uh
You have to overcome your fear
Even if the treatment is a bit extreme
It’s 100% effective haha
Hey bell
No matter what, what if I break it?
It's dangerous
From now on, let’s only treat with herbs.
What is it? The headache is completely gone.
Ah yes
He said he had a very severe cervical disc.
Fortunately, the treatment seems to have gone well.
Oh, that’s why my neck hurt too.
It's me, this damn chronic
Because of a headache
over several years
I can't even go around the hospital
I fixed it
thank you so much thank you
But
The treatment is a bit unusual.
Oh yes, our treatment
It is a medical art that has been handed down since ancient times.
It's a little different
from snake venom
Just extract it here
I'm using it for a specific purpose.
Oh, it's amazing, it's amazing
I first saw the ad
I thought we were dating
Oh, what a surprise.
How much are our marketing activities?
I'm working hard
It can't be like that.
Oh yeah, the medicine is ready. Let's go.
Ah yes ah yes
Thank you teacher, yes sir
Cheer up!
Wait a minute
Are you taking any other medications?
Slowly, slowly
Ah yes
You can eat it in the morning and evening.
uh
Avoid alcohol and fatty foods
Be sure to avoid it, especially during the pig season.
Stay away from the pork posture
Do it, if the pig finds out
It's a very cute animal
What are you doing these days?
A dog at home too
You raise them and you also raise pigs, right?
Uh yeah
Please give me 10,000 won
It's really 10,000 won, yeah
Please give me cash
Okay, yes, please go in. Oh oh.
Now you're moving
oh
You can't do something like that.
Hahaha
Be careful, be careful hahahahaha everything
How much is this?
In total, it is 12.6 million won.
Haha
Please pack everything
How can I pay in installments hahaha?
The word installment
It's annoying to the ears
Oh sorry of course
We will pay you in one lump sum.
Oh right, for a long time
Hey, it's going to be a long time
Oh, there are a lot of people, yeah
The gods of the beginning came from musical instruments
to protect humans
twelve people
sent an angel down to earth
These angels
To cover the world in darkness
with musical instruments
After an immeasurable battle
won and
source of darkness
To seal the gates of hell
It was successful
The mask you see over there
special power
They blocked the instruments
It's being passed down
From then on, our ancestors
Let's sit there
The weather is killer hehe
um
salty
Hehehehehe take it
What is this all about?
What is it, my heart?
I usually
You know I care a lot
It's okay, I don't need it.
no need
Hey
This is good for you
Only things that fit
I picked it and brought it to you.
You bought it with the boss’s money.
Yes, um
I'm sorry to the captain too. Hey, what are you sorry about?
The target is him
I have a lot of money
The monkey saw it
They say they spend their money on toilet paper
Hahahahahahahahaha
working
Don't come here and do this.
many times
I told you
when will you come home
Mirae, ten years have already passed
You guys fall like this
It shouldn't be there
It's my job to protect it
I know
I have to go
I'll contact you
Hey Miriya Miriya
Take this
What on earth did Jaehee receive in her dream?
You're even hiding it from me
It's so good after a long time
Ah
It's killing me
Sit, sit, sit haha ouch
Hey
Ah brother
no how
Why did you come out so quickly?
Yeah, that's right
How did this come out so quickly?
From what I see, Gwangsu cares.
I think you gave it to me
tomorrow
Let’s all say hello together.
yes yes
Hahaha oh my brother called me
who is it
Of course Mr.
Hello
Ah, President Cho Young-soo.
This is Angel Capital Angel Angel Angel
Oh, you're the boss, Angel.
Haha oh my
I work hard to make money
You said you would pay it all back.
Are you glad you came out?
It's good to come out then
Wait a minute
The reason you stole from me was to get money.
This is absolutely crazy.
Oh, because I'm going now
Please wait a moment
Oh yeah on
Yes, yes, Mr. Lee hangs up the phone haha.
Wow
Oh, you know the boss of Angel.
Oh, that big guy
They say they're coming now
If you see it, hit it right away.
yes yes
Seohyun is
Have a cup of coffee with the kids
My brother took care of one thing and immediately
I'll call you
Brother, what's going on?
Oh, I'm saying that because I'm so worried.
I want to watch the fight too, oppa
Alas, we are not ordinary people.
That ear over there
I'm a former dumpling martial arts athlete.
Yes, I am a boxing champion.
Just
Hit a person and splatter blood
Doing this
I don't want to show it to me.
Oh brother
I want to show you only good things
I'll call you quickly
Oh yeah, I'm worried so I'll finish it well
uh uh call me yeah
move fast
Brother
Brother, brother, don’t step forward, I love you
Oh yeah
Oh, move, pack your bags
Let’s go to Itaewon
Okay, don’t go.
He said he would make it so that he could see it.
Citizens’ cooperation and
Please drive safely
Oh why boss
When you arrive
Joyang Su-ae in front
It will be so crowded
Currently operating in the city direction
The cars are right before
Please take a detour at the intersection.
This car goes even if there is no road
This fucking bastard
Hey Mr.
Uh uh uh
Ugh
Mistress
oh
oh oh
ha
you
Wait a minute
here
oh
Now
Now just sign here
It's done
Now, because this is a little lacking
Find this
yes
Okay
Hey guys, here
Arrived okay
Oh, I'll come back, hey
Take care, yeah
Matsuka come to work, come to work
Hey, I'm going, I'm going
I'll go and take care of it by myself.
Hey, don't be so fussy
These are thugs
I'm running it
And today is collection day
I knew we would come
They must have invited a lot of kids.
Are you kidding?
What do you think of me
Just go to the car and wait
Miscellaneous
Now, finish your English well.
I have to take care of that transport today too.
yes yes and me
Angel Capital kids today
It will definitely come, so take care of it.
Yes yes you guys that doksaba
I know you're a guest of Seongmugi.
That angel last time
Kids go to the Philippines without money
I cheated
That angel's
Why are these babies so sweet?
Chase and get all the money
I stole it so much
It's evil
Do you understand the evil candy? Yes
Especially when I get caught by that boss.
Next to me, there, there
baseball bat
That ashtray
I have these things
When it appears
Rush in and kill half of them.
Do you understand? I found you. Come here.
I'll catch up
What are you surprised at?
uh
child
No, I'll solve it
If you're trying to buy me, you can't do that.
let's go
Oh, then why did I go through all that trouble?
So go up there
let's go kid
ok let's go
You have to clear it up a bit, there are more above, be careful.
It's inside the operator.
Hey
You guys are making this up and playing it.
bring my money
Oh, bring my money quickly.
Oh, let go, let go of the child, Mr. Lee.
Baby, bring my money
money my money
IC
Let go, kid.
I won't let you go, I'll tell you to be quiet, I won't let you go, really.
Tell me to be quiet.
Oh, let go
I like the picture
Hey hey hey, grab it, grab it, get it there
catch catch catch
Hey, this time
Because I'm trying to solve it myself
You guys stay still ah
I'm surprised, hey hey hey
Stop it you bastard
Oh what is this?
He speaks
Why are you so impatient?
Calm down for a moment
You take the rest and come.
Oh, my skills are good.
One guy runs away up the stairs
Hey, he’s leaving the building. He’s talking nonsense.
Go down the stairs and find a room for the three of you.
Ah, Mr. Lee
Wow
What is this, you pig?
face what
This crazy pig keeps going
Ah ah
Ah
Get out of the way
Where are you running Mr. Lee?
you guys came here
Well, this is the only time to run away.
I kicked you so hard I can't speak
This is not a concussion.
This is the end of the situation
Okay, I caught that guy.
They said they caught it and it’s easier to breathe
But he's not dead
Oh, did you lose your leg?
The bag is
Got it
I packed my bag of money, okay, let’s withdraw.
I especially added a lot.
yes
Here's the guarantee
What are you talking about, man?
Hahaha it's my uncle
It's my uncle
Haha, why haven’t you come here so far?
I missed you
I was busy. Business is going well.
You know my Sol.
Reduce it during the day
It's so long and there's an uproar over how delicious it is.
Thank you for coming, man.
Thank you
The only person I talk to
It's gold season
Oh, my face really doesn't look good.
Now I'm thinking about my body like this
I also cut down on alcohol.
I also exercise
no i
After exercising for over 5,000 years,
I'm bored
I've lived too long no
Uncle, for a long time
I lived a very long time
We have to protect good people
You're an angel
angel
It's a secret, but who will listen?
I am human
It's been a long time since I stopped protecting
You know, when I was in middle school
Gangsters live in the neighborhood with my mom
all people
I used a stick to chase them away.
I remember it brightly.
I remember
Geumsoon’s mother also sold tteokbokki.
yes
At that time, the uncle was one of those bad guys.
I just scolded them all and they fell apart
That wuddu
and
Save my mom and me too.
so i am mom
I was able to take over the family business.
I'm really happy
No matter how angelic
Protect humans for a long time
It must have been really hard to give it away.
Even your family
Because I sacrificed while losing
You must be tired ugh
Because of selfish people
But man, do you know this?
people
All my gratitude is here
I live with it in my heart
Like me
Ugh humans aren't that bad.
and
Now the devils
It's not a world where things are tough.
You too are finding happiness now, yes
happiness
Our Geumsoon is really
You've really grown up a lot
uh
Oh wait, man, I
I'll bring you lots of delicious food.
I won't take that.
No, please accept it just this once.
Geumsun, no
Why have you been like this since you were young?
Because the child is stubborn
Oh my, you are such a bastard, you are such a bastard
I said we'd see each other earlier.
Where is this little guy?
old
Speak informally to adults
I'm making noises
You're such a bastard that you've been fooled
no i am this friend
Since I was a kid
I guess we used to know each other
So hey
Oh my
This guy is like a thunder behemoth
This guy
I think you drank a lot of the same alcohol.
You, you, are you not full?
No, this guy is really
No, that's right
That’s right, Manbok, the son of a stationery shop.
you pee all the time
Pack salt every morning
You went to get it
you uh
Mr. Taesani, Mr. Taesani
I am Mr. Taesan.
That's right
No, but how can you be so young?
Oh my, Manbok
I’m full of luck, my goodness.
We hahahahahahahaha
This is this son of a bitch
It's been a really long time
How did you stay alive?
Ah, but
How did you not age at all?
Recently, Songwon-gu, Seoul
Jinnae Apartment Redevelopment Complex
in the field
From the Paleolithic era to ancient times
Artifacts believed to be
found in large quantities
This is reporter Heo Jeong-hyeon’s report.
Pumice Age
Starting with earthenware believed to be
along the sedimentary layer
ancient to the top
Artifacts are being excavated
especially
A form that is difficult to specify at a time and
Minerals made up of particles are
discovered
Research at school
together
Showing great interest
The excavated artifacts
National cultural heritage until the 25th
Under investigation at the laboratory
What's strange?
This is it at all
I can't measure it at all.
I think the numbers are too crazy
I found Ogi
Heh this
Hey
Guys, I brought you tteokbokki.
Kang Jae-ya
Won Seung is so talkative.
I also bought your favorite sundae
Have you done it yet?
Why do I have to eat it while it's hot?
um
Ugh
Are you okay?
Because I overdid it
If you proceed with the ritual, your life will be lost.
Ugh
no more
I can't delay time
Ugh
The thread attached to my body shook me for a moment.
rattle rattle rattle
Red Velvet in my burning fist
Wolwol Blazing Fist
When I knock on the blade that cuts through the darkness
split the darkness
Quick quick, even if I look back, I can’t turn back.
Reflected in the eyes of those crazy arguments
Pichchat peeled off and smeared on both fists
Because of him, flames and flames fire
I'm Tiger is the word
Even if I run far, Ye Gung will overtake me
I blackened the chaechae so my throat got sore.
I can't turn it back now
With a fistful of faith
the last
Sparks sparkle in the swinging darkness
name of taesan
Now that I can't stand it
a fistful of
Swinging the last with faith
The name of the world buried in the darkness
Blurred senses
This is a familiar illusion of tragedy
Yesterday becomes a knife that stabs me
I can't trust anyone
My heart is frozen with no place to lean on
Yes, my heart is newly embedded
This bruise I have over there